lyric	type	songTitle	albumTitle		
Do real niggas get to go to heaven?	Thug Life	How Long Will They Mourn Me	Thug Life: Volume 1		
It's kinda hard to be optimistic when your homies lying dead on the pavement twisted	Hard Knock Life	How Long Will They Mourn Me	Thug Life: Volume 1		
I'm trying hard to make amends but I'm losing all my muthafuckin friends	Hard Knock Life	How Long Will They Mourn Me	Thug Life: Volume 1		
They shoulda shot me when I was born. Now I'm trapped in the muthafuckin storm.	Hard Knock Life	How Long Will They Mourn Me	Thug Life: Volume 1		
"They got a nigga sheddin tears, reminiscing on my past fears"	The Game	My Block	Better Dayz		
It appears that I've been marked for death	The Game	My Block	Better Dayz		
My eyes stay teary for all the brothers that are buried in the cemetery	Hard Knock Life	My Block	Better Dayz		
"I ain't givin up on the hood, it's all good when I go back"	The Hood	My Block	Better Dayz		
"Hoes show me love, niggas give me props"	The Hood	My Block	Better Dayz		
Can't explain a mother's pain when her son drops	The Game	My Block	Better Dayz		
Staying strapped forever trapped in this drug life	The Game	My Block	Better Dayz		
Can't sleep cause all the dirt make my heart hurt	The Game	My Block	Better Dayz		
Mislead from childhood where I went astray	The Game	My Block	Better Dayz		
In my heart I felt alone out here on my own	The Game	My Block	Better Dayz		
Used to be a close knit community but now we're all cold strangers	The Hood	My Block	Better Dayz		
Gamin the hoochies hoping I can get to sleep with her	The Game	My Block	Better Dayz		
Alcohol will make a lazy nigga slip and fall	The Game	My Block	Better Dayz		
Growing up in this word where everything is scandalous	The Game	My Block	Better Dayz		
I hit the green just to maintain	The Game	My Block	Better Dayz		
"What is it we all fear, reflections in the mirror?"	The Game	Who Do You Believe In	Better Dayz		
Can't close my eyes cause all I see I terror	The Game	Who Do You Believe In	Better Dayz		
I hate the man in the mirror	The Game	Who Do You Believe In	Better Dayz		
In this society where only getting cash counts	The Game	Who Do You Believe In	Better Dayz		
All the Hennessy and weed can't hide the pain I feel inside	The Game	Who Do You Believe In	Better Dayz		
This life of sin done got the both of us in trouble	Love Life	Never Call U Bitch Again	Better Dayz		
You always stay down for a nigga so that's why I love you	Love Life	Never Call U Bitch Again	Better Dayz		
You always in the mood for love	Love Life	Never Call U Bitch Again	Better Dayz		
It's a complicated world so girl just be a friend	Love Life	Never Call U Bitch Again	Better Dayz		
I swear I'll never call you bitch again	Love Life	Never Call U Bitch Again	Better Dayz		
My enemies think they got me crossed	The Game	Never Call U Bitch Again	Better Dayz		
Tryin to get my money on strong	The Game	Never Call U Bitch Again	Better Dayz		
"I found a partner and a rider, a woman and friend"	Love Life	Never Call U Bitch Again	Better Dayz		
"Never meant to hurt you, can we make this work boo?"	Love Life	Never Call U Bitch Again	Better Dayz		
"I won't deny it, I'm a straight ridah. You don't wana fuck with me"	Thug Life	Ambitionz Az A Ridah	All Eyez On Me		
That's what they screamin as they drill me but I'm hard to kill	Thug Life	Ambitionz Az A Ridah	All Eyez On Me		
Thuggin for life and if you right then nigga die for it	Thug Life	Ambitionz Az A Ridah	All Eyez On Me		
When it's time to die to be a man you pick the way you leave	Thug Life	Ambitionz Az A Ridah	All Eyez On Me		
"For money, I'll have these motherfuckers  buried"	Thug Life	Ambitionz Az A Ridah	All Eyez On Me		
We can do this like gangstas and slug it out or we can do it like punks and punk it out	Thug Life	Thug Luv	The Art of War by Bone Thugs-n-Harmony		
"Until they stop me, bury, murder me, or drop me I got thug love for my nationwide posse"	Thug Life	Thug Luv	The Art of War by Bone Thugs-n-Harmony		
I ain't got no motherfuckin friends	Thug Life	Hit Em Up	All Eyez On Me		
Fuck your bitch and the clique you claim	Thug Life	Hit Em Up	All Eyez On Me		
Fuck peace I'll let them niggas know it's on for life	Thug Life	Hit Em Up	All Eyez On Me		
Five shots couldn't drop me. I took it and smiled.	Thug Life	Hit Em Up	All Eyez On Me		
"Niggas be actin' like they savage, they out to get the cabbage"	Thug Life	2 of Amerikaz Most Wanted	All Eyez On Me		
I live in fear of a felony.	Hard Knock Life	2 of Amerikaz Most Wanted	All Eyez On Me		
I never stop ballin.	Thug Life	2 of Amerikaz Most Wanted	All Eyez On Me		
Release me to the streets and keep whatever's left of me	Thug Life	2 of Amerikaz Most Wanted	All Eyez On Me